老娘今晚最后一笔小费
Well, here it is. My last tip.
只有两块钱
Only $2.
亏我之前还为了那些小气鬼憋住一个屁
And to think, I held in a fart for those cheap bastards.
今晚烂死了
This night sucks.
我们都没赚够明天蛋糕店的材料钱
We don't even have enough to buy supplies for tomorrow.
只能去那家所有商品皆免费的小店拿了
We'll just have to go to that store where everything's free.
太好了 那店还没关门
Oh, good. They're open.
我们得偷偷把这些东西弄出去
And we have to sneak all this stuff out.
阿憨今晚要留下清点库存
Han's staying late to do inventory.
靠 他有需要这么亚洲人吗
Damn it, why does he always have to be so asian?
我们小蛋糕店需要哪些东西来着
Let's see, what do we need for our cupcake shop?
-鸡蛋 糖 -脱衣舞钢管一根
- Eggs, sugar. - A stripper pole?
你到底想不想挣钱啊
Do you want to make money or not?
我们该怎么偷带这些鸡蛋走啊
How are we gonna hide these eggs?
你可以把这些"A级大鸡蛋"
You could put some of those "Grade A large"
藏进你的"A杯小奶罩"里
where there's "Grade A itty-bitties."
嘴贱 不过主意不错
Rude, but I don't hate it.
我估计一边可以塞四到六颗
I can probably fit four to six in each.
真积极正面
So positive!
我就爱你这样"杯"子半满的积极人士
I love that you're a "cup's half full" kind of person.
常来光顾吗
So come here often?
人家第一次来
This is my first time.
-你很漂亮哦 -谢谢夸奖
- Well, you're very pretty. - Oh, thank you.
小心啦 阿憨要过来了
Heads up. Han's coming your way.
要我假装中风吗
Should I fake a stroke?
先说好 如果我三分钟后都没起身
And P.S., if I don't get up in three minutes,
那我就是真中风了
It's a real one.
不用 我来搞定他
No, I'll deal with him.
你继续塞
You keep going.
别停啊 你继续我们就能知道
Keep it up, and we'll finally have an answer
是鸡先来到世上
to the question "What comes first?
还是奥列格[蛋]先"来"啦
The chicken or the Oleg?"
给
Here you go.
我刚在网上找到最棒的玩意了
I just found the greatest thing online.
金与坎耶小孩的超声波照吗
The ultrasound of the Kim and Kanye baby
就是腹中婴儿小屁股被改图加上
where someone photoshopped a "666"
恶魔数字"666"的那张吗
on its little baby butt?
等等 那娃有卡戴珊的基因
Wait, this kid's half Kardashian.
是大屁股被改图才对
Its big baby butt.
哇 那孩子毛都不干就已经出名了
Wow, that baby's already famous for doing nothing...
跟他娘一模一样啊
Just like its mom.
不 我是找到了一个我们可以申请
No, what I found is a site where we can apply
小企业生意拨款的网站
for a small business grant.
里面有几个类别 比如女性专营企业
There's a couple of categories: women-owned business--
不必了 我去过监狱
No thanks. I've been to jail.
已经"专属"过某个女性了
I was already owned by a woman.
也有一类是少数民族拥有啊
There's also a minority-owned category.
你也不知道你的生父是谁
You don't know who your father is,
你又有着异国风的外貌
and you do have an exotic look.
你生父有没有可能是印第安人呢
Any chance he could be native american?
没错 他的名字还叫做
Yes, in fact, I think his name was
逃跑酋长呢
Chief Running Away.
等等
Wait.
你老爸这张牌都不见得需要用
Maybe we don't even need your father.
我们是白人
We are white,
根据上次总统大选时的数据
which according to the last presidential election,
白人现在算少数民族呢
is the new minority.
我们只需要找到一个同样开店的人
So now all we need is a letter of recommendation
来帮我们写封推荐信就行了
from someone who owns another start-up business.
我想找糖果店老板
I was thinking of a recommendation
糖果安迪帮忙写一封呢
from Candy Andy's Sweets and Treats.
信我写好了 他签个名就行了
I've already written it, so he just has to sign it.
你能代我问吗 我不行 他是我前任
Will you ask Andy? I can't, he's my ex.
而且我想把请他帮忙的额度
And I'm saving up my favor
留给寒冷夜晚找他打炮用
for a booty call on a cold night.
我最讨厌请[问]男人帮忙了
I hate asking men for things.
请他们帮忙 问他们姓啥 请他们"停下"
Favors, last names, to stop.
抱歉 能再给我几包低脂糖吗
Excuse me, could I get some more sweet'n low?
你干嘛不从你自己包里拿
Why don't you look in your purse?
我看你偷拿了几包放里面
It's where I saw you put them.
真是太不好意思了
I'm so embarrassed.
不必
Don't be.
我昨晚偷它们的时候就没不好意思
I wasn't when I stole them last night.
安迪怎么说
What did Andy say?
他不见了
He's gone.
-暂离吃饭吗 -是永远走人
- For lunch? - Forever.
他真的走了
The man is gone.
他的店都空了
His store is empty.
天啊 感觉好伤心哦
Oh, my God, this is so sad.
对啊 糖果飞了
I know. There goes the candy.
我的炮友也飞了
And my booty call.
-连张字条都没留吗 -也没留包口香糖吗
- He didn't even leave a note? - Or a Razzle?
别想着糖了
Forget the candy.
我们不应该来谈谈
Are we not gonna talk about the fact
我的前男友不见最后一面就溜走的事吗
that my ex-boyfriend left without so much as a peep?
这下好了 害我想吃棉花糖[看一眼]
Great. Now I want Peeps.
麦克斯
Hey, Max.
今天有幸跟你结婚吗
Is today the day we're gonna get married?
当然好啊 阿米尔
Sure, Amir.
因为我这辈子的梦想
'Cause my dream in life is to be detained
就是在度蜜月的班机上被扣留四小时
for four hours on our honeymoon flight.
麦克斯 你知道我是在这国家土生土长的吧
Max, you do know I was born in this country, right?
你在美国出生的啊 你几岁了
You were born here? How old are you?
黑暗零点三十岁吗
About zero dark thirty?
你妈是在沃尔玛生的你 对吧
Yeah, you were born in a Walmart, right?
不然你觉得人们常说的
Where do you think the expression
"打扫一下第12排地板"是怎么来的
"Clean up on aisle 12" comes from?
卡洛琳
Hey, Caroline,
你还为你吓跑你男朋友的事情泄气吗
you bummed you drove your boyfriend out of town?
我得声明 我才没把他吓跑路了呢
For the record, I did not chase Andy away.
我们是和平分手的
We ended our relationship well.
是啊 所以我才要在大半夜
Right, that's why I helped him move out
帮忙他搬家
in the middle of the night.
你把人家玩坏了
Man, you messed that up.
你这人太自我了
So self-involved.
阿米尔 你炮火有点猛烈啊
Coming in a little hot, Amir.
中东人不能带武器 不然我嘴炮扫死你
Yeah, guns ablazin'. If I was allowed to carry them.
阿米尔 你太酷了[你是炸弹]
Oh, Amir. You're the bomb.
你瞧咱们
Look at us.
我们就像是浪漫喜剧版的《国土安全》
We're like Homeland, if it was a rom-com.
不用读啦 阿憨
You don't have to read it, Han.
只是一封标准的正常推荐信而已
It's just a standard letter of recommendation.
少唧唧歪歪 乖乖签字就对了
Don't be a bitch. Just sign it.
没亲自读过的文件
I'm not comfortable putting my name
我没法放心签下名
on a document I haven't read.
我懂 但你还是少唧唧歪歪
I understand, but don't be a bitch.
乖乖签字就是了
Just sign it.
"麦克斯自制小蛋糕是一个
"Max's homemade cupcakes is
蒸蒸日上 发展强劲的小生意"
an up-and-coming powerhouse business."
我不能签这个
I can't sign this.
这信比我的约会网站个人资料还鬼扯
This has more lies than my Okcupid profile.
少唧唧歪歪 快乖乖签字
Don't be a bitch. Just sign it.
我也帮你们说一句 姑娘们
That one's on me, girls.
我签了字 就是合伙骗人
If I sign this, it's lying.
我可能会被遣送出境
I could get deported.
我可是只差一次家访 就能领养贵宾狗了呢
And I'm one home inspection away from a poodle adoption.
贵宾狗啊 挺好的啊
A poodle? That's cool.
你们衣服能换着穿
You can share sweaters.
快点啦 叽歪弟
Hurry up, bitch.
今晚之前得把那信寄出去
The deadline to mail that is tonight.
如果你们是想逼人签字
Well, if you just wanted to steamroll someone,
干嘛不去逼她男朋友安迪签字呢
why didn't you get your boyfriend, Andy, to sign it?
他们分手了
They split.
他昨晚最后一面都没见就跑了
He left last night without a peep.
靠 我又想起棉花糖[见一面]了
Damn it, now I'm thinking about those Peeps again.
我早就担心你们俩会感情触礁了
Oh, I was worried you two wouldn't make it.
你满脑子都是想着你的生意
You always have your mind on business,
而安迪又是个灵魂轻松的人
and Andy was such an easy spirit.
你是想说灵魂向往自由吧
I think you mean "free spirit."
"灵魂轻松"是灵魂已死的人
Easy Spirit is a shoe worn by people
才会去穿的鞋子品牌
whose spirits have died.
我有两双
I have two pairs.
行 不签就还给我
Okay, fine. Give it back.
我找其他做生意的人吧
I'll find someone else with a business.
请苏菲签如何 她有个小生意啊
What about Sophie? She owns a small business,
又乐意为他人奉献
and she loves to give,
虽然她更爱收下我的"爱"
not as much as she loves to receive.
但我不确定苏菲的家政生意
I'm not so sure Sophie's cleaning business
是不是百分百合法呢
is totally, well, legal.
我们以前给她打过工
I mean, when we worked for her,
我们薪水支票的备忘栏
on the memo line of our paycheck,
她写了"结肠镜检查"呢
she wrote "Colonoscopy."
我替她声明 她的家政生意
And for the record, Sophie's cleaning business
绝对是合法的
is totally legit.
器官买卖的生意可能就不是了
Her organ-trading might not be.
算了 卡洛琳
Forget it, Caroline.
我们亲自把他遣送出境算了
We might deport you ourselves.
反正用个快递盒就够装了
All we need is a Fedex box.
卡洛琳 过来一下
Um, Caroline. Come over here.
我应该能够帮你哦
I think I can help you with that.
谢了 厄尔 但是你没有小生意啊
Thanks, Earl, but you don't have a small business.
我裤裆里的"生意"从没有人怀疑过它小哦
The size of my business has never been in question.
而我虽然没有什么小生意
And I may not have a business,
但...
But...
李阿憨有啊
Han Lee does.
麦克斯 你看 厄尔伪造了阿憨的签名
Max, look. Earl forged Han's signature.
原来他的签名是这样啊
That's what his signature looks like.
我伪造他签名时 都是画个凯蒂猫而已
When I forge it, I just draw a picture of Hello Kitty.
想知道你的未来吗
You want to know your future?
-不必 谢了 -你确定吗
- No, no thanks. - You sure?
我有个关于你爱情的预言呢
I have a message about your love life.
你在睡觉吗
Are you asleep?
麦克斯 我有话想跟你谈
Max? Max, I really need to talk.
直接进来发泄不就得了
Oh, just come in and get it over with.
其他人都这样
Everybody else does.
抱歉 麦克斯 我真的想跟你谈一下
Max, I'm sorry, but I really need to talk.
我去了餐厅附近的算命店
I went to the fortune teller near the diner,
她说我这辈子注定一生无爱
and she told me that I'd never find love in my life.
算命都是骗人的把戏
Fortune-telling's a scam.
"你的月亮与天王星相位 这辈子都没男人
"You'll never find a man, your moon's in Uranus,
天王星上本来就没男人"
no man will ever be in Uranus."
我认识你的第二天就能编这些给你听了
I could've told you that the second day I met you.
求你了 麦克斯 听我说五分钟就好
Please, Max, just listen for five minutes.
过来嘛 我给你泡杯茶
Come over here. I'll make you some tea.
还喝茶 你当我是凯特王妃她妹啊
Tea? Who am I, Pippa Middleton?
给我烤个松饼吃吃 我就考虑听听
Toast me an eggo waffle and maybe I'm listening.
我们本来是要留到
Well, we were saving that waffle
特殊时刻才吃的呢 不过好吧
for a special occasion, but okay.
栗宝 我们现在要吃掉你的生日松饼啦
Chestnut, we're eating your birthday waffle now.
真不知道我干嘛还要惹他生气
I don't know why I'm pissing him off.
他可能是我这辈子唯一的男人了
he's gonna be the only man in my life.
我真不敢相信你花十块钱去找神婆
I can't believe you blew $10 on a psychic.
你就不能跟其他寂寞的白妞一样
Why didn't you just buy a Skinnygirl margarita
买瓶玛格丽塔借酒浇愁吗
like all the other lonely white chicks?
我花了50块
I spent $50.
我还买了一块挡坏运的水晶[音似坏犹太人]
I bought a crystal that protects me from bad juju.
你也不需要因此讨厌犹太人吧
Hey! There's no reason to get anti-semitic.
你还花钱买不能吸食的水晶[冰毒]
You spent money on crystal you can't snort?
你脑子是哪里有病啊
What is wrong with you?
我吓到了嘛 不想要一生无爱
I freaked out. I didn't want it to be true.
会是真的吗 麦克斯
Is it true, Max?
我真的会一生无爱吗
Am I never gonna find love?
安迪是我唯一的希望吗
Was Andy my one chance?
我因为想成功而抛弃了唯一的爱吗
Did I screw it up because I wanted success?
大家说的真的对吗
Was everyone right?
就给一块松饼 也问太多问题了吧
That is a lot of questions for one waffle.
而且那块松饼呢
And where is that waffle?
你在家也是个烂服务员
You're a bad waitress at home too.
这么晚 会是谁啊
Who could that be?
不知道 让我请示一下四方神灵
I don't know. Let me consult the spirits.
是谁啊
Who is it?
是苏菲
It's Sophie.
没错就是我
Yeah, it's me,
有着非法生意的坏女人
The shady lady with the illegal business.
卡洛琳 你得给我道歉
Yeah, and Caroline, you owe me an apology
要不然我会摘下这耳环
or I will take out these hoops,
然后跟你大战一番
and we will get into it, girl.
我警告你哦
Yeah, and I warn you,
我在老家时 可是有不少极限战斗的经验
I did some extreme fighting in Warsaw.
极限战斗 这么酷啊
Extreme fighting? That's awesome.
对啊 他们会把一大块起司丢饲料槽里
Yeah, they would throw a big hunk of cheese in a trough
村里的姑娘就会抢上去大打出手
and let all the village girls just go at it.
抱歉 苏菲
Sorry, Sophie.
只是当时觉得伪造个签名
It just seemed like a better business decision
会对我们生意比较好嘛
to go with the forgery.
那是什么
What is that?
是松饼吗
Is that a waffle?
好吧 原谅你了
Okay! You are forgiven.
靠 我连一口都没吃到
Damn it. I didn't even get a bite.
白起床跟忍着不喝酒了
I'm awake and sober for nothing.
苏菲 你相信灵媒吗
Sophie, do you believe in psychics?
才不信呢 那是骗人的
Oh, no. That's all fake.
我以前认识一个吉普赛灵媒家庭
You know, I knew a family of gypsy psychics
但他们甚至预测不到
who couldn't even predict
他们会全家葬身火海
that they would all die in a barn fire.
姑娘们 抱歉打扰
Hey, girls. Sorry to interrupt,
苏菲之前答应我要帮我又黄又厚的脚趾甲
but Sophie promised to rub antifungal cream
擦灰指甲药膏呢
on my thick, yellow toenails.
奥列格过来吧
Oleg, come over here.
我边吃边帮你擦
I'll do it in between bites.
你害怕得不到的就是这个吗
This is what you're afraid you're missing?
这就是爱情啊
Because this is a relationship.
麦克斯 我是认真的
Seriously, Max.
我真的想要有个爱人
That's something I really want.
但看来我这辈子是无缘了
And now I'm never gonna have it.
你也来吧 宝贝 我有两只脚呢
Get in there, baby. I have two feet.
有意思
Interesting.
神婆居然需要在门上挂个铃铛
She's a psychic, but she needs a bell
才能知道有人来了
to tell her someone's here.
麦克斯 不要逼我来嘛
Max, please don't make me do this.
我不想再听到任何坏事了
I don't want to hear any more bad things.
不会发生什么坏事啦
Nothing bad's gonna happen.
她会告诉你
She's gonna tell you
你有一个充满爱的光明未来
you have a bright, love-filled future
不然我会狠狠踹她的水晶"球"
Or I'm gonna kick her in the crystal balls.
你们好 姑娘们
Hello, girls.
我一吃完饭就给你们预测未来
I'll tell you your future as soon as I finish eating.
几分钟就好
It'll only take a minute.
戒烟之后 我就像饿死鬼投胎一样
Since I quit smoking, I eat like a prisoner.
过来坐下 冥思下自己的愿望和梦想
Come, sit, ruminate on your wishes and dreams.
我的愿望是 你能把钱还给我的朋友
Well, my wish is that you give my friend her money back,
我的梦想是
and my dream is that
成为梅西·埃丽奥特的伴舞员
I'm a backup dancer for Missy Elliott.
很好 自作聪明的人
Great. A wise-ass.
你们到底想不想知道自己的未来
Do you want to know your future or not?
你已经告诉过我了
Um, you already told me my future.
所以我们才来这里
That's why we're here.
你说我会一生无爱了
You said I'd never find love.
我什么时候说的
When did I say that?
还有你 小悍妞 千万不要说
And you, tough guy, don't say,
"你是神婆你会不知道吗"
"Well, you're the psychic."
或许她真的是神婆 因为我的确是个悍妞
Maybe she is a psychic, because I am a tough guy
而且我也打算这么说
and I was gonna say that.
我很难记住每个人
You know, it's hard to remember.
我一天见那么多可怜的单身妹
I see a lot of sad, single girls.
但现在仔细看看你
But looking at you right now,
我的话也不无道理
it makes sense.
给
And here.
把你骗人的水晶拿回去
Take your phony crystal back.
我连这是不是真水晶都说不准
And I'm not so sure this is a real crystal.
这看起来像腋下除臭剂之类的
It looks like one of those vegan deodorant things.
把我们的钱还来
And we want our money.
好吧 你刚干嘛了
Oh, okay. What just happened?
我对你下诅咒了
I put a curse on you.
麦克斯 你说过不会有坏事发生的
Max, you said nothing bad was gonna happen!
我又不是神婆 不过她也不是
Well, I'm not a psychic, and neither is she.
尽管笑吧 小鬼
Laugh, buster.
你人生的一切都会变得不如意
Nothing in life will go your way,
你会永远被不祥的乌云笼罩着
and you will live under a dark cloud.
请问那朵乌云会跟
Will this dark cloud merge
现在笼罩在我上方的乌云合体吗
with the current dark cloud above me
还是默默地飘在旁边
or fly alongside of it?
我们也不想麻烦你
Look, we don't want to trouble you,
但如果你能高抬贵手解除诅咒
but if you could remove the curse
再顺手把你衣服上的面也弄掉...
and possibly that noodle on your blouse...
不是吧 你刚是不是...
Oh, no. Did you just--
顺便诅咒了你
Cursed you too.
这样吧
Tell you what.
50块就替你们解咒
I'll lift both curses for 50,
不然 妹子你不给钱
or else your whole life
人事物都掉下来
will come crashing down all around you.
除非我在你店里给性器官穿了环
The only way I'm giving a strange woman 50 bucks
否则我不会随便给陌生女人50块钱
is if I'm walking out of here with a genital piercing.
这个我也能做哦
I do that as well.
不要相信什么诅咒 没有的事
Don't believe in curses, never have.
当初詹妮弗·马丁还不是
Not since Jennifer Martin told me
因为我睡了她男人 而诅咒我下地狱
I was going to hell for sleeping with her boyfriend.
也没事啊
But I didn't.
最后还跟他一起出席了返校派对呢
I just ended up going to homecoming with him.
麦克斯 我们必须回去付钱给她
Max, we have to go back and pay her.
我们的人生已经够苦的了
Our lives are hard enough.
身边不需要有人事物掉下来
We don't need things to come crashing down around us.
放轻松 不会有任何东西掉下来的
Relax. Nothing's coming crashing down around us.
别跳 保罗
Don't jump, Paul!
保罗 别跳
Paul, don't jump!
保罗 谁是保罗
Paul? Who's paul?
他在楼顶干嘛啊
And what is he doing on the roof?
好吧
Okay.
是保罗这个人掉下来
That was paul's life that came crashing down,
不是我们
not ours.
麦克斯 我们都知道
Max, I think we all know that
我是一名高学历女性
I'm a highly educated woman
不相信诅咒这种事
who doesn't really believe in curses,
但今晚我要把我们挣的每一分钱
but I am putting every penny we make tonight
都放进"解除诅咒"基金里
in the "lift the curse" Fund.
我再跟你说最后一遍
And I'm gonna tell you one more time,
我们不会为了某个愚蠢的诅咒
we're not spending another 50 bucks
再多花50块钱
on some stupid curse.
一个人从天上掉下来啊
A body fell from the sky!
保罗倒霉吃到烂迷幻蘑菇
Paul got a bad batch of shrooms.
跟诅咒一点关系都没有
It had nothing to do with the curse.
人人都知道不应该在二楼以上
Everyone knows you don't take psychedelics
吃迷幻药
above the second floor.
业余的倒霉蛋
Poor amateur bastard.
我们需要钱来买必需品 比如食物
And we need our money for essentials, like food
和我在一元店看见的那企鹅像
and the penguin statue I saw at the dollar store.
上面写着"冷爆了"[冷静]
The one that says "Chill out."
所以 冷静
So chill out.
卡洛琳 我觉得很内疚
Caroline, I feel bad about
没帮在你的推荐信上签名
not signing your letter of recommendation.
所以我自己写了一封 名字也签好了
So I wrote one myself and signed it.
给
Here.
你真好
That's so nice of you.
"工作超级努力的卡洛琳·钱宁
"The extremely hardworking Caroline Channing,
把人生全部奉献给事业
who has devoted her life to business
心无旁骛 身无旁人"
and nothing and no one else."
阿憨 这封信是要写苦苦求财
Han, this is supposed to be about getting a loan,
而不是写哭哭求爱
not being alone.
我完全明白 妹子
I totally get it, girl.
我也形影自守
I'm alone as well.
为求商场得意 努力不懈
We have our eyes on the prize,
因此情场失意 床上空虚
so our beds are empty.
但我偶尔也会花钱找人陪睡哦
But occasionally, I pay for it.
刚才阿憨暗示了
Did Han just intimate
他偶尔会花钱叫鸡吗
that he occasionally gets a hooker?
这幸运的小淫棍
Lucky bastard.
估计他叫鸡还有儿童折扣呢
He probably gets a child's discount.
麦克斯 看 不幸的未来已经开始了
Max, look. The future's already happening.
连在阿憨的信里 我都是孤身一人
Even in Han's letter, I'm alone.
我现在最能接近爱情的方法
The only chance for a love life I have now
就是跟阿憨分摊招妓费用
is going halfsies on a hooker with Han.
我们必须得解除诅咒
We have to reverse the curse now.
新闻快讯 人人都是被诅咒的倒霉蛋
News flash: everybody is cursed.
去年你万贯家财没了
You lost your money last year.
严格说来 我身上从来没发生过好事
Literally nothing good has ever happened to me.
阿憨从四年级就没长过个子
Han hasn't grown since the fourth grade.
奥列格的脚趾甲看起来像薯片
Oleg's toenails look like Fritos.
厄尔生在美国史上
And Earl was born black
黑人最惨时代中
at the eighth or ninth-worst time
排行第八或第九的年代
to be a black man in America.
你看清楚吧 这里就是诅咒之谷
Look around, it's the valley of the damned.
你举出一个没被诅咒的人啊
Name one person who isn't cursed.
伙计们
Hey, guys!
我刚在人行道上捡到100块
I just found a $100 bill on the sidewalk!
我请所有人喝酒
Drinks for everyone!
麦克斯 把那瓶高级白兰地打开
Max, pop open the fancy brandy.
你要是同意让我在店里装根钢管
"Fancy brandy" is gonna be my stripper name
"高级白兰地"就会是我的艺名哦
if you ever let me put in that pole.
苏菲 跟你说哦
Sophie, guess what?
我们回灵媒那控诉她
We went back to that psychic to complain,
结果她对我们俩下诅咒了
and she put a curse on us.
你们俩被诅咒啦
Oh. You're cursed?
但就像你说的 白痴才信 对吧
But it's stupid, like you said, right?
对对 白痴才信
Yeah, yeah. That's stupid.
没错
Yeah.
她有提到我的名字吗
Did she mention me?
没啦
No.
她只是对我们下咒 然后说
She just cursed us and said
不给钱 我们周围的人事物都会掉下来
our whole lives would come crashing down around us.
30 40 50块
and 30, 40, 50.
诅咒解除了
The curse is lifted.
你好像没弄到我 那我的诅咒呢
Oh, I don't think you got me. What about my curse?
做戏做全套
Talk about phoning it in.
你不能挥舞个羽毛还是转转头
Couldn't you wave a feather or spin your head
甚至是呕吐一下之类吗
or throw up or something?
那要额外收费
That's extra.
其实呢 我今晚心情很不错
You know what? I'm in a good mood tonight.
我今天只抽了15根烟
I got through the whole day on 15 cigarettes
吃了一整个大蛋糕就满足了
and one sheet cake.
我送一次免费塔罗算命给悍妞吧
I'm gonna give tough guy a free reading here.
免费是指付50块后免花费吗
Oh, free, as in the $50 you just shook us down for?
一开始就不应该试着戒烟
Should never have quit. Okay.
你的未来马上就能算出
Future coming right at you.
我看到了你会有个快乐人生
I see that you will have a happy life.
我 快乐吗
Me, happy?
母亲 戴上帽子 我们可以走人了
All right, get your hat, mother. We're leaving.
还有很大一笔钱将要入你手
And I see a large sum of money coming your way.
一万元以上哦
Over $10,000.
麦克斯 是那个拨款
Max, it's the grant.
我们申请了一万二 是这个吗
We applied for $12,000. Is that it?
当然
Sure.
尽管你有个悲惨的童年
And in spite of your bad childhood...
她知道你有悲惨的童年耶
She knew you had a bad childhood.
拜托 谁的童年不悲惨
Come on, every childhood is bad.
又小又笨 总够不着东西
You're stupid. You can't reach stuff.
超悲催啊
It's rough.
尽管如此
In spite of it,
我看到你的未来有爱人与儿女相伴
I see great love and children in your future.
麦克斯
Max.
我吗 等等
Me? No, wait.
你是不是接收到她的未来啦
You must be picking up on her vibes.
再检查一下
Check again.
没 就是你有爱人与儿女
No, great love and children
在未来伴你左右
will be part of your future.
她会孤独终老
She will die alone.
够了 我受不了了
Okay, well, that's all I can take.
我不要在这坐等下一个保罗掉下来
I'm not gonna sit here and wait for the other Paul to fall.
-走吧 麦克斯 -别别别
- Let's go, Max. -No, no, no, no.
别走 等等
No, no. Wait.
她绝对是算错了 对吧
She obviously got it wrong. Didn't you?
没 她就是会孤独终老
Nope. Still dying alone...
但是会在事业上取得大成功
with nothing but her great success.
抱歉 没听清 你再说一遍
I'm sorry, I'm sorry. What?
我看到了你的未来会有大成功
I see great success in your future.
真的吗 谢天谢地
You do? Oh, thank God.
我会功成名就吗 多成功啊
I'm gonna have success? How big a success?
亲爱的 超级成功
Oh, honey, it's so big,
成功到你都意识不到自己有多孤独
you won't even know you're alone.
好啦 你们走吧
All right, go.
祝你们长命百岁 一生健康
May you live a long and healthy life.
记得带上帽子手套
And put on your hat and gloves.
我预测要下雪了
I'm predicting snow.
才不会下雪呢
It's not going to snow.
顶多也就是30岁男人们如雨坠落
At most, it's gonna rain 30-year-old dudes.
她也不是多灵嘛
Maybe she isn't so psychic.
不要不信邪了 麦克斯
Stop fighting it, Max.
你会找到爱人然后过得开心
You're gonna find love and be happy,
而我会超级成功
and I'm gonna be successful.
你听到了吗 纽约
You hear that, New York?
我将要功成名就 然后孤独终老
I'm gonna be successful and alone!
你再喊 就要被人先抢后奸了
And robbed and raped if you keep calling that out.
而成功的就是从我把
And it all started when I dropped
拨款申请表投入
that grant application into that mailbox
那正被拆除带走的邮筒开始的
that those guys are unbolting and taking away.
怎么回事
What's going on?
听过电邮吗
It's called emails.
我们要把邮筒拆了 现在都没人寄信了
We're getting rid of this. No one mails anything anymore.
有啊 我昨天才投进去呢
Yes, they do. I did yesterday.
我们的一万二就靠那封信了
And our $12,000 depends on it.
抱歉啦 美女
Sorry, doll.
这邮筒已经除役一周了呢
This box has been out of commission for a week.
而根据神婆说的 她下面的"邮筒"
According to a psychic, her box is gonna be
将"除役"一辈子呢
out of commission forever.
这必须得跟他们说啊
We had to tell him.
你想我骗政府公仆吗
You expect me to lie to a city employee?
看来我们是得不到那笔拨款了
So I guess we're not getting that grant.
那灵媒说错了
The psychic was wrong.
她说的估计没一样会实现
Maybe nothing she said is gonna come true.
我都说了 那是骗人的
I told you, it's a scam.
麦克斯 你瞧
Max, look.
下雪了
It's snowing.
她预测会下雪呢
And she predicted snow.
妈的 我会有小孩啊
Oh, crap! Am I gonna have kids?
她雪预测对了 但钱却没有
So she was right on snow, but not on the money.
这样怎么算啊
So what is it?
我到底会还是不会孤独终老啊
Am I or am I not gonna die old and alone?
我们谈这个干嘛啊
Why are we even talking about this?
我们都不知道活不活得过这冬天
We're probably not gonna make it through the winter.
对了 如果你先死了
if you die first,
我绝对会吃你哦
I am totally eating you.
我知道你会的
Oh. I know.
而且
And besides,
没人能鱼与熊掌兼得啦
no one person can get it all.
你说得对
You're right.
一个人不行 那两个人呢
No one person can, but what about two?
你有爱人与孩子
You'll have the love and the kids
而我有成功
and I'll have success.
我们可以分享啊 就像我们现在分小费
Maybe we can share, like we share our tips
或像我们分享你枕套里发现的饼干一样
or that wheat thin we found in your pillowcase.
你是想跟我以后的爱人上床吗
Are you asking to bang my great love?
我是无所谓啦 我到时肯定也是腻了他
Which is fine with me, becaue I'm already bored
然后开始睡他的牌友
and sleeping with his poker buddy.
这样吧 我们交换
In fact, let's switch.
你可以拿走我的爱人 让我来孤独终老
You can have my great love, and I'll die alone.
麦克斯 你不会想孤独终老的
Max, you don't want to die alone.
我但求孤独一死啊
I am dying to die alone.